One seed can change everything
Vesper is a science fiction, drama, adventure film directed by Kristina Buožytė.
After the collapse of Earth's ecosystem, Vesper, a 13-year-old girl struggling to survive with her paralyzed Father, meets a mysterious Woman
with a secret that forces Vesper to use her wits, strength and bio-hacking abilities to fight for the possibility of a future.
Vesper, played by Raffiella Chapman.
Jonas, played by Eddie Marsan.
Camellia, played by Rosy McEwen.
Darius, played by Richard Brake.
Elias, played by Edmund Dehn.
Jug, played by Melanie Gaydos.
Vesper (released in France as Vesper Chronicles) is a 2022 science fiction film directed by Kristina Buožytė
and Bruno Samper, starring Raffiella Chapman, Eddie Marsan, Rosy McEwen and Richard Brake.
Set in a bleak post-apocalyptic Earth, it follows the
eponymous 14-year-old girl skilled in biohacking.
It was selected to compete at the 2022 Karlovy Vary International Film Festival.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.